advancedmp3players.co.uk 2019-04-12

# Security & Privacy – The Privacy Policy of Advanced Headphones

\- Advanced MP3 Players are committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

\- We collect information about you for 2 reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service.

\- We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent.

\- We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing email from us or from another trader in the future.

\- Please understand that even if you choose to opt out from sharing your email with another trader in the future, we will still share your contact and billing information with third party companies upon your acceptance of their offer.

\- The type of information we will collect about you includes: 

  * your name 
  * address 
  * phone number 
  * email address 
  * credit/debit card details 

\- We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. 

\- The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

\- The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.

\- If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.

\- From time to time, we may market certain third party services through our site.  Should you choose to accept an offer from a third party, we will pass your relevant personal information, including name and credit/debit card number, to that third party which may have its own privacy policy which describes how it uses your personal information and how it may export personal data outside the EEA.

\- If you have any questions/comments about privacy, you should email or telephone us. Full contact details are available on the 'Contact Us' page on the Advanced MP3 Players website. 

**Cookie Policy:**

\- We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.  
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

This website uses the following cookies:

Item| Cookies| Purpose| More information  
---|---|---|---  
 **amp3sid**|  amp3sid| This cookie is a session identifier, it allows things like your shopping basket data to be saved and for each visit to our website to be identified individually.|   
 **Javascript cookies**|  Occassional/Possible| Unrecognised Javascript _probably_  sets a cookie, but this can't be confirmed automatically.|   
 **Google Loader**|  Occassional/Possible| Uses Google's dynamic Javascript loader, which _could_  itself load code that sets a cookie, but this can't be confirmed automatically.|   
 **Google Analytics**|  _utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz*| Collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.| [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html). You can choose to [opt out of Google Analytics](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).  
 **VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE**|  VISITOR_INFO1_LIVE| This cookie performs a custom function for this website and helps to store basic (non personalised) visitor information.|   
 **Dynamic Javascript cookies**|  Occassional/Possible| Unrecognised Javascript _could_  sets a cookie, but this can't be confirmed automatically.|   
This test cannot detect rare cookies which only appear after a form is submitted. This site uses forms - you should manually check for extra cookies set by these to be sure.  
  
* _These cookies are provided by a third party who could change their cookies in future outside of our control. We will review this policy regularly for any such changes._

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
